Steven Kulp

4336 Idaho Street #5 San Diego, CA 92104 sdkulp@gmail.com (503) 475-2777

Full-Stack Web Developer

stevenkulp.github.io linkedin.com/in/steven.kulp github.com/stevenkulp

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer and UX/UI enthusiast with an eye for design and a passion for creativity. Backed by 4+ years of office and project management experience, and looking to utilize personal strengths, skills, and passions in a professional setting.

Proficiencies

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Ruby, Python, SQL

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Rails, Bootstrap

Design Tools: Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch

Other: Github, Trello, Logic X

Experience

Web Developer Intern. PermitDocs (March 2019 - Present)

- · Creating a Chrome browser extension to augment the PermitDocs platform into a user's web browsing experience.
- Developing a RegEx-focused data scraper built in Python to be incorporated into the platform.
- · Gaining invaluable experience and knowledge as a result of working directly in the Web Development industry.

Web Developer Student, LEARN Academy (November 2018 - March 2019)

- Built a variety of web and mobile applications using front-end and back-end programming languages.
- Created and solved detailed and complex logic problems through the use of critical thinking.
- · 400+ hours of hands-on training via solo programming, pair programming, and mob programming.

Operations Associate, RSI Security (March 2018 - November 2018)

- Managed Accounts Payable, tracking all outgoing expenses and eliminating/preventing unnecessary spending.
- Coordinated and researched events and opportunities to maximize sales opportunities and company presence.
- Evaluated company metrics and KPIs to pinpoint areas of strength as well as areas for improvement.

Assistant Property Manager, C&R Real Estate (June 2016 - March 2018)

- Recipient of "2017 Award of Excellence" for strong project management skills during massive renovation project.
- Maintained an exceptional retention rate of current tenants, with consistent resident satisfaction.
- Implemented sales and marketing campaigns to improve property visibility, minimizing unit turnaround times.

Account Manager, Sirennet (December 2014 - June 2016)

- Maintained client accounts, serving as the primary point of contact for the client.
- Constructed winning bids for client projects, and arranged timely and accurate deliveries of large/complex orders...
- · Managed company's retail Amazon vendor page, leading to increased revenue and seller rating.

Various Retail Positions, Quiznos Subs, Macy's, Wizer's Market (May 2007 - December 2014)

Education

B.A. Psychology and Graphic Design, Portland State University (2007 - 2012)